Guide to the Gerald H. Anderson Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings, Lectures, Research Files, 1957-2012; Series II
  - Regarding booklength works
    - Biographical Dictionary of Christian Mission
      - Articles File
        - Flierl, Johann (Box 11, Folder 1188)
        - Flynn, John (Box 11, Folder 1189)
        - Focher (Fucher), Jean (Box 11, Folder 1190)
        - Fonseca, Angelo da (Box 11, Folder 1191)
        - Forbin-Janson, Charles de (Box 11, Folder 1192)
        - Ford, Francis X. (Box 11, Folder 1193)
        - Forgacs, Gyula (Box 11, Folder 1194)
        - Forman, Charles William (1821-1894) (Box 11, Folder 1195)
        - Forman, Charles William (1916-) (Box 11, Folder 1196)
        - Formosus (Box 11, Folder 1197)
        - Forsyth, Christina Moir (Box 11, Folder 1198)
        - Foucauld, Charles Eugene de (Box 11, Folder 1199)
        - Foucquet, Jean Francois (Box 11, Folder 1200)
        - Fox, Henry Watson (Box 11, Folder 1201)
        - Fox Charles Eliott (Box 11, Folder 1202)
        - Frame, (Mrs. Murray) alice Browne (Box 11, Folder 1203)
        - Francescon, Luigi (Box 11, Folder 1204)
        - Francis of Assisi (Box 11, Folder 1205)
        - Francis, Mabel (Box 11, Folder 1204)
        - Franck(e), August (Box 11, Folder 1205)
        - Francke, August Hermann (Box 11, Folder 1206)
        - Franson, Fredrik (Box 11, Folder 1207)
        - Fraser, Alexander Garden (Box 11, Folder 1208)
        - Fraser, Donald (Box 11, Folder 1209)
        - Fraser, James Outram (Box 11, Folder 1210)
        - Fraser, John Andrew Mary (Box 11, Folder 1211)
        - Fraser, Kenneth (Box 11, Folder 1212)
        - Freed, Paul (Box 11, Folder 1213)
        - Freeman, John Joseph (Box 11, Folder 1214)
        - Freeman, Thomas Birch (Box 11, Folder 1215)
        - Freinademetz, Joseph (Box 11, Folder 1216)
        - Frietag, Anton (Box 11, Folder 1217)
        - Frelinghuysen, Theodorus (Box 11, Folder 1218)
        - French, Thomas Valpy (Box 11, Folder 1219)
        - French, Evangeline and Francesca (Box 11, Folder 1220)
        - Frey, Joseph Samuel Christian Frederick (Box 11, Folder 1221)
        - Freytag, Walter (Box 11, Folder 1222)
        - Fridelli (Friedel) Xaver Ehrenbert (Box 11, Folder 1223)
        - Fridolin (Fridold) (Box 11, Folder 1224)
        - Fries, Karl (Box 11, Folder 1225)
        - Friesen, Abraham (Box 11, Folder 1226)
        - Fritz, Samuel (Box 11, Folder 1227)
        - Frois, Luis (Box 11, Folder 1228)
        - Frost, Henry Weston (Box 11, Folder 1229)
        - Frumentius (and Aedesius) (Box 11, Folder 1230)
        - Fuller, Andrew (Box 11, Folder 1231)
        - Fuller, Jennie (Box 11, Folder 1232)
        - Fulton, T. C. (Box 11, Folder 1233)
        - Fumasoni- Biondi Pietro (Box 11, Folder 1234)
        - Furmn, Charles T. (Box 11, Folder 1235)
        - Gabet, Joseph (Box 12, Folder 1236)
        - Gabra, Michael. See Ghebra, Michael (Box 12, Folder 1237)
        - Gaebelein, Arno C. (Box 12, Folder 1238)
        - Gairdner, William Henry Temple (Box 12, Folder 1239)
        - Gale, James Scarth (Box 12, Folder 1240)
        - Galland, Emmanuel (Box 12, Folder 1241)
        - Gallus (Gall) (Box 12, Folder 1242)
        - Galvin, Edward J. (Box 12, Folder 1243)
        - Gamewell, Francis (Frank) and Mary (Box 12, Folder 1244)
        - Graces, Julian (Box 12, Folder 1245)
        - Gardiner, Allen Francis (Box 12, Folder 1246)
        - Garnier, Charles (Box 12, Folder 1247)
        - Garr, Alfred Goodrich (Box 12, Folder 1248)
        - Gaspais, Auguste (Box 12, Folder 1249)
        - Gebauer, Paul (Box 12, Folder 1250)
        - Geddie, John (Box 12, Folder 1251)
        - Gensichen, Hans-Werner (Box 12, Folder 1252)
        - George, David (Box 12, Folder 1253)
        - George, Eliza Davis (Box 12, Folder 1254)
        - Gerald, Jean-Joseph (Box 12, Folder 1255)
        - Gerardin, Joseph (Box 12, Folder 1256)
        - Gerbillon, Jean Francois (Box 12, Folder 1257)
        - Gericke, Christian (Box 12, Folder 1258)
        - Geyer, Francis Xavier (Box 12, Folder 1259)
        - Ghebra, Michael (Box 12, Folder 1260)
        - Giannecchini, Doroteo (Box 12, Folder 1261)
        - Giannelli, Jose (Box 12, Folder 1262)
        - Gibson, John Campbell (Box 12, Folder 1263)
        - Giffen, John Kelly (Box 12, Folder 1264)
        - Gih (Ji), Andrew (Box 12, Folder 1265)
        - Gilbert, Nathaniel (Box 12, Folder 1266)
        - Gilbert, Nathaniel (Box 12, Folder 1267)
        - Gill, William (Box 12, Folder 1268)
        - Gilman, Frank Patrick (Box 12, Folder 1269)
        - Gilmour, James (Box 12, Folder 1270)
        - Gilmour, John (Box 12, Folder 1271)
        - Glass, Frederick (Box 12, Folder 1272)
        - Glass, Frederick (Box 12, Folder 1273)
        - Glasser, Arthur F. (Box 12, Folder 1274)
        - Glazik, Josef (Box 12, Folder 1275)
        - Glen, William (Box 12, Folder 1276)
        - Glover, A. E. (Box 12, Folder 1277)
        - Glover, Robert Hall (Box 12, Folder 1278)
        - Goarnisson, jean-Louis (Box 12, Folder 1279)
        - Gnecci-Sldi, Organtino (Box 12, Folder 1280)
        - Gobat, Samuel (Box 12, Folder 1281)
        - Goble, Jonathan (Box 12, Folder 1282)
        - Gockel, Mary (Box 12, Folder 1283)
        - Goddard, Josiah (Box 12, Folder 1284)
        - Goes, Bento de (Box 12, Folder 1285)
        - Goforth, Jonathan (Box 12, Folder 1286)
        - Goforth, Jonathan and Rosalind (Smith) (Box 12, Folder 1287)
        - Gogerly, Daniel John (Box 12, Folder 1288)
        - Goh, Hood King (Box 12, Folder 1289)
        - Goldie, Hugh (Box 12, Folder 1290)
        - Goldie, John F. (Box 12, Folder 1291)
        - Goldsack, William (Box 12, Folder 1292)
        - Gollmer, Charles Andrew (Box 12, Folder 1293)
        - Gomer, Joseph (Box 12, Folder 1294)
        - Gomer, Mary Green (Box 12, Folder 1295)
        - Gomes, David (Box 12, Folder 1296)
        - Gonzalez, Justo (Box 12, Folder 1297)
        - Gonzalez de Santa Cruz, Roque (Box 12, Folder 1298)
        - Good, Adolphus Clemens (Box 12, Folder 1299)
        - Goodall, Norman (Box 12, Folder 1300)
        - Goode, Francis (Box 12, Folder 1301)
        - Goodell, William (Box 12, Folder 1302)
        - Gordon, Adoniram Judson (Box 12, Folder 1303)
        - Gordon, Andrew (Box 12, Folder 1304)
        - Gordon, George Maxwell (Empty) (Box 12, Folder 1304)
        - Goreh, Nehemiah Nilakantha (Box 12, Folder 1305)
        - Gorham, Sarah E. (Box 12, Folder 1306)
        - Gossner, Johannes Evangelista (Box 12, Folder 1307)
        - Gottlieb, C. G. (Box 12, Folder 1308)
        - Goupil, Rene (Box 12, Folder 1309)
        - Govan, William (Box 12, Folder 1310)
        - Gowans, Walter (Box 12, Folder 1311)
        - Gowans, Walter (Box 12, Folder 1312)
        - Goward, Wlliam E. (Box 12, Folder 1313)
        - Goyau, Georges (Box 12, Folder 1314)
        - Grajales, Francisco Lopez de Mendoza (cf. also Lopez de Mendoza) (Box 12, Folder 1315)
        - Graham, James, III (Box 12, Folder 1316)
        - Graham, John Anderson (Box 12, Folder 1317)
        - Graham, William (Billy) Frank (Box 12, Folder 1318)
        - Grandin, Vital Justin (Box 12, Folder 1319)
        - Grant, Anthony (Box 12, Folder 1320)
        - Grant, Asahel and Judith S. (Campbell) (Box 12, Folder 1321)
        - Grant, Charles (Box 12, Folder 1322)
        - Grant, G. C. and Ida (Box 12, Folder 1323)
        - Grant, Judith (Campbell) (Box 12, Folder 1324)
        - Grassman, Andrew (Box 12, Folder 1325)
        - Graul, karl (Box 12, Folder 1326)
        - Gray, Robert (Box 12, Folder 1327)
        - Graybill, Anthoy Thomas (Box 12, Folder 1328)
        - Green, Samuel Fiske (Box 12, Folder 1329)
        - Greene, Elizabeth "Betty" (Box 12, Folder 1330)
        - Gregg, Jessie (Box 12, Folder 1331)
        - Gregory I (The Great) (Box 12, Folder 1332)
        - Gregory Thaumaturgus (Box 12, Folder 1333)
        - Gregory VII (Hildebrand) (Box 12, Folder 1334)
        - Greogory XV (Alessandro Ludovisi) (Box 12, Folder 1335)
        - Gregory VI (Bartholomeo Cappellari) (Box 12, Folder 1336)
        - Greogory the Illuminator (Box 12, Folder 1337)
        - Grenfell, George (Box 12, Folder 1338)
        - Grenfell, Wilfred Thomason (Box 12, Folder 1339)
        - Grentrup, Theodor (Box 12, Folder 1340)
        - Gribble, Ernest (Box 12, Folder 1341)
        - Gribble, John Brown (Box 12, Folder 1342)
        - Griffiths, Bede (Box 12, Folder 1343)
        - Griffiths, David (Box 12, Folder 1344)
        - Grignion de Montfort Louis Marie (Box 12, Folder 1345)
        - Grimke, Charlotte Forten (Box 12, Folder 1346)
        - Griswold, Hervey Dewitt (Box 12, Folder 1347)
        - Groot (Grotius), Hugo de (Box 12, Folder 1348)
        - Grossman, Guido (Box 12, Folder 1349)
        - Groves, Anthony Norris (Box 12, Folder 1350)
        - Groves, C. P. (Box 12, Folder 1351)
        - Grubb, Kenneth George (Box 12, Folder 1352)
        - Grubb, Norman (Box 12, Folder 1353)
        - Grubb, Wilfred Barbrooke (Box 12, Folder 1354)
        - Gruber, Johannes (Box 13, Folder 1355)
        - Grundemann, Peter Reinhold (Box 13, Folder 1356)
        - Grundler, J. E (Box 13, Folder 1357)
        - Gsell, Francis (Box 13, Folder 1358)
        - Gual, Pedro (Box 13, Folder 1359)
        - Gubernatis, Dominicus de (Box 13, Folder 1360)
        - Gudwal (Box 13, Folder 1361)
        - Guebriant, Jean-Baptiste Budes de (Box 13, Folder 1362)
        - Guerrant, E. O. (Box 13, Folder 1363)
        - Guinness, Henry Grattan (Box 13, Folder 1364)
        - Gulick, Alice (Box 13, Folder 1365)
        - Gulick, Luther Halsev and Louisa Mitchell (Lewis) (Box 13, Folder 1366)
        - Gulick, Orramel Hinckley and Ann Eliza (Clark) (Box 13, Folder 1367)
        - Gulick, Peter J. and Fanny Hinckley (Thomas) (Box 13, Folder 1368)
        - Gulliford, H. (Box 13, Folder 1369)
        - Gundert, Hermann (Box 13, Folder 1370)
        - Gunning, Jan Willem (Box 13, Folder 1371)
        - Gurney, Samuel (Box 13, Folder 1372)
        - Gusinde, Martin (Box 13, Folder 1373)
        - Gutmann, Bruno (Box 13, Folder 1374)
        - Gutzlaff, karl Friedrich August (Box 13, Folder 1375)
        - Gwynne, Llewellyn Henry (Box 13, Folder 1376)
        - Hadfield, octavius (Box 13, Folder 1377)
        - Hagenauer, Friedrich (Box 13, Folder 1378)
        - Hahn, Carl Hugo (Box 13, Folder 1379)
        - Hahn, Heinrich (Box 13, Folder 1380)
        - Haines, Byron (Box 13, Folder 1381)
        - Hale, Matthew (Box 13, Folder 1382)
        - Hale, Sarah J. (Box 13, Folder 1383)
        - Hall, Elizabeth Garland (Box 13, Folder 1384)
        - Hall, Gordon (Box 13, Folder 1385)
        - Hall. Marian (Box 13, Folder 1386)
        - Hall, Sherwood (Box 13, Folder 1387)
        - Hall, Ronald Owen (Box 13, Folder 1388)
        - Hallbeck, H. P.Halliwell, Leo B. and Jessie (Box 13, Folder 1389)
        - Halley, James Theodore (Box 13, Folder 1390)
        - Hambroeck, Antonius (Box 13, Folder 1391)
        - Hamlin, Cyrus (Box 13, Folder 1392)
        - Hamlin, James (Box 13, Folder 1393)
        - Han, Kyung Jik (Box 13, Folder 1394)
        - Handt, john C. S. (Box 13, Folder 1395)
        - Hanlin Henry (Box 13, Folder 1396)
        - Hannington, James (Box 13, Folder 1397)
        - Hanxleen, johann Ernst (Box 13, Folder 1398)
        - Happer, A. P. (Box 13, Folder 1399)
        - Harada, Tasuku (Box 13, Folder 1400)
        - Haraldsson, Olav (Box 13, Folder 1401)
        - Hardy, Robbert Spence (Box 13, Folder 1402)
        - Haringke (Box 13, Folder 1403)
        - Harling, Otto Von (Box 13, Folder 1404)
        - Harms, Ludwig (Box 13, Folder 1405)
        - Harnack, Adolf Von (Box 13, Folder 1406)
        - Harris, George Kaufelt (Box 13, Folder 1407)
        - Harris, Merriman Colbert (Box 13, Folder 1408)
        - Harris, William Wade (Box 13, Folder 1409)
        - Harrison Paul Wilberforce (Box 13, Folder 1410)
        - Hartenstein, Karl (Box 13, Folder 1411)
        - Hartenmann, (Joseph Alois) Anastasius (Box 13, Folder 1412)
        - Hartmann, Maria (Box 13, Folder 1413)
        - Hastings, Eurotas Parmelee (Box 13, Folder 1414)
        - Hastings, Harry (Box 13, Folder 1415)
        - Haven, Jens (Box 13, Folder 1416)
        - Haweis, Thomas (Box 13, Folder 1417)
        - Hawaweeny, Raohael (Box 13, Folder 1418)
        - Hawkins, Ernest (Box 13, Folder 1419)
        - Hawley, Gideon (Box 13, Folder 1420)
        - Haymaker, Edward M. (Box 13, Folder 1421)
        - Hayward, Victor E. W. (Box 13, Folder 1422)
        - Heath, George Reinke (Box 13, Folder 1423)
        - Heber, Reginald (Box 13, Folder 1424)
        - Hebich, Samuel (Box 13, Folder 1425)
        - Heckewelder, John (Box 13, Folder 1427)
        - Heim, karl (Box 13, Folder 1428)
        - Heine, Carl (Box 13, Folder 1429)
        - Heinrich, Maurus (Box 13, Folder 1430)
        - Helm, Lucinda Barbour (Box 13, Folder 1431)
        - Hemans, JamesHenry Emmanuel (Box 13, Folder 1432)
        - Henderson, Ebenezer (Box 13, Folder 1433)
        - Henderson, James (Box 13, Folder 1434)
        - Henriquez, Henrique (Box 13, Folder 1435)
        - Henry, Antonin-Marcel (Box 13, Folder 1436)
        - Henry of Uppsala (Box 13, Folder 1437)
        - Hepburn, James Curtis (Box 13, Folder 1438)
        - Hepburn, J. D. (Box 13, Folder 1439)
        - Heras, Henry (Box 13, Folder 1440)
        - Herman of Alaska (Box 13, Folder 1441)
        - Hermosilla, Hieronymus (Box 13, Folder 1442)
        - Hernandez, Venancio (Box 13, Folder 1443)
        - Herschell, Redley Haim (Box 13, Folder 1444)
        - Herrer, Andres (Box 13, Folder 1445)
        - Herron, Walter (Box 13, Folder 1446)
        - Hetherwick, Alexander (Box 13, Folder 1447)
        - Heurnius, Justus Von (Box 13, Folder 1448)
        - Heyer, John Christian Frederick (Box 13, Folder 1449)
        - Heyling, Peter (Box 13, Folder 1450)
        - Hiebert, Nicholai N(icholai) (Box 13, Folder 1451)
        - Higginbottom, Sam (Box 13, Folder 1452)
        - Hildegard of Bingen (Box 13, Folder 1453)
        - Hill, David (Box 13, Folder 1454)
        - Hill, John Henry (Box 13, Folder 1455)
        - Hill, Mary (Box 13, Folder 1456)
        - Hinderer, David (Box 13, Folder 1457)
        - Hinderer, David and Anna Martin (Box 13, Folder 1458)
        - Hinsley, A. (Box 13, Folder 1459)
        - Hislop, Stephen S. (Box 13, Folder 1460)
        - Hitchcook, John William (Box 13, Folder 1461)
        - Hobson, Benjamin (Box 13, Folder 1462)
        - Hocking, William Ernest (Box 13, Folder 1463)
        - Hodges, Melvin Lyle (Box 13, Folder 1464)
        - Hoecken, Christian (Box 13, Folder 1465)
        - Hodgkin, H. T. (Box 13, Folder 1466)
        - Hogson, Thomas Laidman (Box 13, Folder 1467)
        - Hoekendijk, Johannes (Box 13, Folder 1468)
        - Hoevel, Wolter Robert Van (Box 13, Folder 1469)
        - Hofinger, Johannes (Box 13, Folder 1470)
        - Hoffman, C(adwllader) Colden (Box 13, Folder 1471)
        - Hoffmann, Johannes Baptist (Box 13, Folder 1472)
        - Hoffmann, Ludwig Friedrich Wilhelm (Box 13, Folder 1473)
        - Hofmeyr, Stefanus (Box 13, Folder 1474)
        - Hogan, J. Philip (Box 13, Folder 1475)
        - Hogg, Alfred George (Box 14, Folder 1476)
        - Hogg, JohnHogg, Laurie (Box 14, Folder 1477)
        - Holland, Henry Tristram (Box 14, Folder 1478)
        - Holly, James Theodore (Box 14, Folder 1479)
        - Holmes, Elkanah (Box 14, Folder 1480)
        - Holsten, Walter (Box 14, Folder 1481)
        - Holtker, Georg (Box 14, Folder 1482)
        - Honda, Yoichi (Box 14, Folder 1483)
        - Hong Xiuquan (Box 14, Folder 1484)
        - Honoratus (Box 14, Folder 1485)
        - Hooper, Handley (Box 14, Folder 1486)
        - Hoornbeeck, Johannes (Box 14, Folder 1487)
        - Hoover, James Matthew (Box 14, Folder 1488)
        - Hoover, Willis Collins and Mary (Box 14, Folder 1489)
        - Hopkins, Samuel (Box 14, Folder 1490)
        - Hore, Edward Coode (Box 14, Folder 1491)
        - Horne, Melvill (Box 14, Folder 1492)
        - Horton, Azariah (Box 14, Folder 1493)
        - Horvath, Jene (Box 14, Folder 1494)
        - Hoste, Dixon Edward (Box 14, Folder 1495)
        - Hough, George H. (Box 14, Folder 1496)
        - Howard, Leonora (Box 14, Folder 1497)
        - Howe, Gertrude (Box 14, Folder 1498)
        - Howells, George (Box 14, Folder 1499)
        - Hoy, William Edwin (Box 14, Folder 1500)
        - Hsi, Pastor (Box 14, Folder 1501)
        - Hsu, Kuang-Ch'i (Box 14, Folder 1502)
        - Huc, Evariste Regis (Box 14, Folder 1503)
        - Huddleston, Trevor (Box 14, Folder 1504)
        - Huelgel, Frederick (Box 14, Folder 1505)
        - Hueting, A. (Box 14, Folder 1506)
        - Hughes, Thomas Patrick (Box 14, Folder 1507)
        - Hulbert, Homer B. (Box 14, Folder 1508)
        - Huldane, Robert (Box 14, Folder 1509)
        - Hulstaert, Gustave (Box 14, Folder 1510)
        - Hume, Edward J. (Box 14, Folder 1511)
        - Hume, Robert Allen (Box 14, Folder 1512)
        - Hume, Robert Wilson (Box 14, Folder 1513)
        - Hunnicutt, Benjamin Harris (Box 14, Folder 1514)
        - Hunt, Bruce F. (Box 14, Folder 1515)
        - Hunt, John (Box 14, Folder 1516)
        - Hunt, Phineas R.Hunter, George W. (Box 14, Folder 1516)
        - Hunter, Leslie Stannard (Box 14, Folder 1517)
        - Hurburt, Charles E. (Box 14, Folder 1518)
        - Hut, Hans (Box 14, Folder 1519)
        - Hyde, John (Box 14, Folder 1520)
        - Hynd, David (Box 14, Folder 1521)
        - I Sung-Hun, Peter (Box 14, Folder 1522)
        - Ibiam, Francis Akanu (Box 14, Folder 1523)
        - Ibuka, K. (Box 14, Folder 1524)
        - Iglehart, Charles Wheeler (Box 14, Folder 1525)
        - Ignatius of Loyola (Box 14, Folder 1526)
        - Ihmels, Carl (Box 14, Folder 1527)
        - Ilminski, Nicholai Ivanovitch (Box 14, Folder 1528)
        - Ingalls, Murilla B. (Box 14, Folder 1529)
        - Imad-ud-Din (Box 14, Folder 1530)
        - Inglis, John (Box 14, Folder 1531)
        - Ingoli, Francesco (Box 14, Folder 1532)
        - Ingram, James Henry (Box 14, Folder 1533)
        - Inman, Samuel Guy (Box 14, Folder 1534)
        - Innocent (Innokenti Veniaminov) (Father John Popov) (Box 14, Folder 1535)
        - Innocent IV (Box 14, Folder 1536)
        - Intorcetta, Prospero (Box 14, Folder 1537)
        - Irnenaeus (Box 14, Folder 1538)
        - Isaiah of Rostov (Box 14, Folder 1539)
        - Isakovich, Nikolai (Box 14, Folder 1540)
        - Isakwitsch, Nil (Box 14, Folder 1541)
        - Isenberg, Karl Wilhelm (Box 14, Folder 1542)
        - Isherwood, Annie (Box 14, Folder 1543)
        - itzem, Julio (Box 14, Folder 1544)
        - Ivanovskii, Nikolai (Box 14, Folder 1545)
        - Ivanosky, Pavel (Box 14, Folder 1546)
        - Jabavu, Davidsn Don Tengo (Box 14, Folder 1547)
        - Jabavu, John Tengo (Box 14, Folder 1548)
        - Jaca, Francisco Jose de (Box 14, Folder 1549)
        - Jackson, sheldon (Box 14, Folder 1550)
        - Jacobis, Justin de (Box 14, Folder 1551)
        - Jaeschke, Heinrich Augustus (Box 14, Folder 1552)
        - Jameson, William (Box 14, Folder 1552a)
        - Janes, leroy Lansing (Box 14, Folder 1553)
        - Janicke, Johann (Box 14, Folder 1554)
        - Jaffray, Robert A. (Box 14, Folder 1555)
        - Jansz, Pieter (Box 14, Folder 1556)
        - Janzen, Aaron A. (Box 14, Folder 1557)
        - Janssen, Arnold (Box 14, Folder 1558)
        - Jaricot, Pauline-Marie (Box 14, Folder 1559)
        - Jarlin, Stanislas (Box 14, Folder 1560)
        - Jartoux, Pierre (Box 14, Folder 1561)
        - Javouhey, Anne-Marie (Box 14, Folder 1562)
        - Jefferson, John Clark (Box 14, Folder 1563)
        - Jellesma, Jelle Eeljes (Box 14, Folder 1564)
        - Jessup, Henry Horris (Box 14, Folder 1565)
        - Jen, Ch'eng-Yuan (Box 14, Folder 1566)
        - Jensen, Christian (Box 14, Folder 1567)
        - Jesaja (Box 14, Folder 1568)
        - Jing Jing (Box 14, Folder 1569)
        - Joacymph, Father (Box 14, Folder 1570)
        - Jocz, Jacob (Box 14, Folder 1571)
        - Jogues, Isaac (Box 14, Folder 1572)
        - Johanns, Pierre (Box 14, Folder 1573)
        - John, Griffith (Box 14, Folder 1574)
        - John of Monte Corvino (Box 14, Folder 1575)
        - John of Segovia (Box 14, Folder 1576)
        - Johanssen, Ernst (Box 14, Folder 1577)
        - John of Plano Carpini (Plano de Carpine) (Box 14, Folder 1578)
        - John XXIII (Anggelo Giuseppe Roncalli) (Box 14, Folder 1579)
        - John Paul II (Karol Wojtyla) (Box 14, Folder 1580)
        - Johns, David (Box 14, Folder 1581)
        - John, Christoph Samuel (Box 14, Folder 1582)
        - Johnson, A. Wetherell (Box 14, Folder 1583)
        - Johnson, Amelia (Baker). (Box 14, Folder 1584)
        - Johnson, James (Box 14, Folder 1585)
        - Johnson, Mammie (Box 14, Folder 1586)
        - Johnson, Samuel (Box 15, Folder 1587)
        - Johnson, William Augustine Bernard (Box 15, Folder 1588)
        - Johnson, William Percival (Box 15, Folder 1589)
        - Johnston, T. S. (Box 15, Folder 1590)
        - Jomier, Jacques (Box 15, Folder 1591)
        - Jones, Charles Colcock Sr. (Box 15, Folder 1592)
        - Jones, Clarence Wesley (Box 15, Folder 1593)
        - Jones, David (Box 15, Folder 1994)
        - Jones, David Picton (Box 15, Folder 1595)
        - Jones, E(li) Stanley and Mabel Lossing (Box 15, Folder 1596)
        - Jones, Edward (Box 15, Folder 1597)
        - Jones, Eliza Grew (Box 15, Folder 1598)
        - Jones, Evan and John B. (Box 15, Folder 1599)
        - Jones, George Heber (Box 15, Folder 1600)
        - Jones, John (Box 15, Folder 1601)
        - Jones, John Peter (Box 15, Folder 1602)
        - Jones, John Tavlor (Box 15, Folder 1603)
        - Jones, Lewis Bevan (Box 15, Folder 1604)
        - Jones, Mabel Lossing (Box 15, Folder 1605)
        - Jones, Nancy (Box 15, Folder 1606)
        - Jones, T. Jesse (Box 15, Folder 1607)
        - Jones, William Henry (Box 15, Folder 1608)
        - Jordan, John Baptist (Francis Mary of th Cross) (Box 15, Folder 1609)
        - Jordan, Lewis G(arnett) (Box 15, Folder 1610)
        - Jonenhans, Joseph Friedrich (Box 15, Folder 1611)
        - Jowet, William (Box 15, Folder 1612)
        - Juanmarti, Jacinto (Box 15, Folder 1613)
        - Judd, Gerrit Parmele and laura (Fish) (Box 15, Folder 1614)
        - Judd, Walter (Box 15, Folder 1615)
        - Judson, Adoniram (Box 15, Folder 1616)
        - Judson, Ann Hasseltine (Box 15, Folder 1617)
        - Judson, Emily Chubbuck (Box 15, Folder 1618)
        - Judson, Sarah Hall Boardman (Box 15, Folder 1619)
        - Julian (Box 15, Folder 1620)
        - Junius, Robertus (Box 15, Folder 1621)
        - Junod, Henri Alexandre (Box 15, Folder 1622)
        - Justin Martyr (Box 15, Folder 1623)
        - Juvenaly (Box 15, Folder 1624)
        - Kaahumanu, Queen of Hawaii (Box 15, Folder 1625)
        - Kafarov, Petr Ivanovich (Box 15, Folder 1626)
        - Kafarof, Piotre Ivanovitch (Box 15, Folder 1627)
        - kagame, Alexis (Box 15, Folder 1628)
        - Kagawa, Toyohiko (Box 15, Folder 1629)
        - Kahler, Christiane (Box 15, Folder 1630)
        - Kahler, Martin (Box 15, Folder 1631)
        - Kahn, Ida (Box 15, Folder 1632)
        - Kalbermatter, Pedro (Box 15, Folder 1633)
        - Kalkar, Christian (Box 15, Folder 1634)
        - Kalley, Robert Reid (Box 15, Folder 1635)
        - Kals, Jan Willem (Box 15, Folder 1636)
        - Kam, Joseph (Box 15, Folder 1637)
        - Kamawe, Wanyoike and Wanjau (Box 15, Folder 1638)
        - Kamma, F. C. (Box 15, Folder 1639)
        - Kamwana, Elliot Kenan (Box 15, Folder 1640)
        - Kanamore, Tsurin "Paul" (Box 15, Folder 1641)